{
    "id": "74b97541eafc4cbd97515b80e95fbc76",
    "title": "Adjectives Or Adverbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Janet is a ................................. girl.",
            "description": "Here the adjective beautiful modifies the noun girl.",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "beatifully"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1680ef0fa7814594a6975a990062ef03"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children sang .....................................",
            "description": "Here the adverb beautifully modifies the verb sang.",
            "answers": [
                "beautiful",
                "beautifully"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "680b35cfe68b48da879c0e9d69687989"
        },
        {
            "question": "The radio is too ................................. Please turn down its volume.",
            "description": "Adjectives can be the complement of a verb of incomplete predication (is/am/are/was/were). Adverbs cannot be used like this. ",
            "answers": [
                "loud",
                "loudly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb55d849e81542339ff081ab0b147da9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you speaking so ................................?",
            "description": "We use the adverb loudly to modify the verb speaking.",
            "answers": [
                "loud",
                "loudly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb33d7edf5c24d1aa9ade237db610ad7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a .................................... learner.",
            "description": "Fast can be an adjective and an adverb. There is no such word as fastly.",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "71dd95d9483349f98ac89c034be2b4c2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know him .................................. well.",
            "description": "Quite is the adverb. There is no such word as quitely.",
            "answers": [
                "quite",
                "quitely",
                "quietly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ef4be21dfcf4538a31f6fe9e24fd771"
        },
        {
            "question": "Proofread your work ...................................... before submitting it.",
            "description": "Here the adverb carefully modifies the verb proofread.",
            "answers": [
                "careful",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab5b35940b794e77829f0ed15179934c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You have done an ....................................... job.",
            "description": "Here we use the adjective excellent to modify the noun job.",
            "answers": [
                "excellent",
                "excellently"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22fe9a516a744ce6a3fd1d5394d4f69f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I thought I would pass the test ..................................., but I failed after all.",
            "description": "Here we need the adverb easily to modify the verb pass.",
            "answers": [
                "easy",
                "easyly",
                "easily"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "84244a8b248f41e29377ef7007379300"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ...................................... had any rest since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b04bd03057849df9339531540c14e1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have been having a lot of headaches of .............................",
            "description": "Of late is similar to lately.",
            "answers": [
                "late",
                "lately"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1735e0cebcbc4102823d24bbf38bba04"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was very .................................... of the plan.",
            "description": "Adjectives can be the complement of a verb of incomplete predication (is/am/are/was/were). Adverbs cannot be used like this. ",
            "answers": [
                "critical",
                "critically"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84898c85b1634c46a7a40c73eacfc6d9"
        }
    ]
}